lyricsplayground.com 2019-04-23

# NOTICES, INFORMATION and AGREEMENTS

**_VISITOR AGREEMENT_**

Welcome to **International Lyrics Playground**. Please read this visitor agreement; by using this service, you accept its terms. 

The Web is an evolving medium; we may change the terms of this agreement from time to time. By continuing to use the service after we post any such changes, you accept this agreement, as modified. 

_**Privacy**_ _The Information We Collect_

The information gathered through this website falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to our website through optional registration or e-commerce transactions, and (2) tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through our site. Third party service providers on or linked to by our website, such as vendors of products and services offered through our site, may be gathering information, as well. 

International Lyrics Playground respects the privacy of our users. Under no circumstances will International Lyrics Playground, it's host or it's owners ever willfully divulge user information to any third parties. This includes user/viewer email address or any other personally identifiable information. 

_Cookies_

To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique number, a sort of user ID, if you will, that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won't know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie can't read unrelated data off your hard drive. Our advertisers and third party service providers may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we don't control. 

_Browser level information_

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our site, including the type of browser software you use and your IP address. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site. 

_Information Collected By Third Parties_

We may use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our website. Advertiser does not use your name, address, email address, or phone number to deliver Internet ads. Advertiser does use information about your browser and Web surfing to determine which ads to show you. 

_Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies_

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? 

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on International Lyrics Playground displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit International Lyrics Playground and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers (International Lyrics Playground) better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users / viewers may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

_Converant Media_

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information,  
you can visit http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml 

* * *

We invite you to send in your questions or comments about lyricsplayground.com , or to bring to our attention any material you believe to be inaccurate. Please send such comments, including a copy of any material you wish to discuss, to the attention of the Agreement Manager- the-webmaster@lyricsplayground.com 

If you are an owner of intellectual property who believes your intellectual property has been improperly posted or distributed via one of our Web sites, please notify us by sending e-mail to our Agreement Manager -the-webmaster@lyricsplayground.com. 

The material that appears on International Lyrics Playground is for informational and entertainment purposes only. Despite our efforts to provide useful and accurate information, errors may appear from time to time. Before you act on information you've found on our site, you should confirm any facts that are important to your decision. International Lyrics Playground is not responsible for, and cannot guarantee the performance of, goods and services provided by our advertisers or others to whose sites we link. A link to another Web site does not constitute an endorsement of that site. 

Although we make International Lyrics Playground freely accessible, we don't intend to give up our rights, or anyone else's rights, to the materials appearing on the service. You are free to display and print for your personal, non-commercial use information you receive through International Lyrics Playground But you may not otherwise reproduce any of the materials without the prior written consent of the owner. You may not distribute copies of materials found on International Lyrics Playground in any form (including by e-mail or other electronic means), without prior written permission from the owner. Of course, you're free to encourage others to access the information themselves on International Lyrics Playground and to tell them how to find it. 

We welcome links to our service. You are free to establish a hypertext link to this site so long as the link does not state or imply any sponsorship of your site by International Lyrics Playground. Link Exchanges will only be approved by the Webmaster. Links to International Lyrics Playground must be displayed in a prominent location, eg., the 'home page' or a 'links page' easily accessible to site visitors and search engine bots. Links on subsequent pages are not acceptable for the Link Exchange. International Lyrics Playground will display a text link on the International Lyrics Playground Links Page. Links displayed on International Lyrics Playground does not constitute an endorsement to any products or services. International Lyrics Playground is not responsible for content found on other websites and provides these links as a service and convenience only. Links to sites found to have sexual or criminal content will not be considered for the Link Exchange. 

Hotlinking to ANY files on International Lyrics Playground is monitored and strictly forbidden Hotlinking may result in the banning of your site IP. Offsite linking to our search utility is also forbidden. 

_Exponential_

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
